Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Trade Unions PE.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Trade Unions
1819-2011
1880-2002
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Tamiment Library
PE.001
49.25 Linear Feet in 48 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 3 shared boxes
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Trade Unions (1819-2011, bulk 1880-2002), an artificial collection of vertical files, was accumulated gradually over the years as staff set aside ephemera that was relevant to Tamiment Library's collecting focus but did not belong in discreet collections. This collection consists of contracts, constitutions, flyers, clippings, reports, pamphlets, brochures, press releases, and other printed ephemera created by or related to trade unions, or connected with the labor or trade unionism movements.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Arrangement
Collection is organized into 25 series; one for titles starting with numerals, and one for each letter of the alphabet except X and Z, as no files started with those letters. Files are arranged alphabetically by file title.
Series are arranged alphabetically.
Historical Note
The Tamiment Library, New York University, a special collection documenting the history of United States radicalism, labor, and progressive social action, accumulated this artificial collection of printed ephemera gradually over the years through purchases, donations, standing orders with publishers, trade unions and other organizations, and through exchanges with other special library collections via the Collectors' Network, which was organized by Russell Benedict at the University of Nevada in the 1970s and promoted through his newsletter Top Secret. Tamiment Library staff added materials to this collection on a regular basis.
Scope and Content Note
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Trade Unions (1819-2011, bulk 1880-2002) is composed of printed ephemera related to trade unions, one of the primary collection focuses of the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives. This collection includes files created by trade unions that were part of or of interest to members of the trade unionism and labor movements. Organizations represented include trade unions and labor groups organized at the local, national, and international levels. Examples include the American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE), the Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.): New York Chapter, the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), and the Service Employees International Union (SEIU). These organizations are documented by constitutions, contracts, agreements, by-laws, memoranda, reports, and printed ephemera such as clippings, flyers, broadsides, leaflets, catalogs, press releases, programs, and other printed ephemera arranged alphabetically by organization.
Separated Materials
Posters have been separated from this collection and placed in the Tamiment/Wagner Poster and Broadsides Collection; photographs, political buttons, artifacts, and other materials that are not printed ephemera have also been separated from the collection and placed in the appropriate collections at Tamiment.
In June 2025, four issues of UNITE! magazine housed in Box 49 were removed from the collection and placed into the Maggie Block Papers (TAM 698).
Custodial History
The provenance of the materials is varied. Items were obtained through purchases, donations, standing orders with publishers, arrangements with labor unions and other organizations, exchanges with other libraries, and ongoing collecting by Tamiment staff.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials in this collection have been compiled by the Tamiment Library. The accession number associated with this collection is NPA-2000-231.
In 2025, materials from accession 2019.056, which is associated with Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Subjects (PE 029), were transferred to this collection.
Collective labor agreements.; Strikes and lockouts -- United States.; Publications (documents); Labor unions and communism.; Labor unions -- Elections -- New York (State) -- New York.; Leaflets (printed works); Printed ephemera.; Pamphlets.; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century.; Labor unions -- United States.; Labor unions; Broadsides (notices); Agreements.; Labor unions -- Organizing -- United States.; Contracts; Constitutions.; Bylaws (administrative records); Brochures.; Labor movement -- United States -- History; Labor movement -- New York (State) -- New York -- History; Fliers (printed matter); Strikes and lockouts.; Clippings (information artifacts); Labor unions -- New York (N.Y.); Labor movement -- United States.; Labor movement.; Labor unions -- United States -- History; Labor -- United States.
- Numeric, 1938-2002; 1.5 Linear Feet in 1 record carton and 1 manuscript box
  - 1199: Benefits Newsletter, 1998-1999 (Box 1)
  - 1199: Bread and Roses Cultural Project I, 1979-2002 (Box 1)
  - 1199: Bread and Roses Cultural Project II, 1979-2002 (Box 1)
  - 1199: Circular Letters, 1975-1989, undated (Box 1)
  - 1199: Davis, Leon, 1972-1992 (Box 1)
  - 1199: Drug and Hospital Employees Union, 1963 (Box 1)
  - 1199: Drug and Hospital Employees Union: Manhattan Eye, Ear and Throat Hospital Strike of 1962 (Box 1)
  - 1199: Drug and Hospital Employees Union I, 1962-1971, undated (Box 1)
  - 1199: Drug and Hospital Employees Union II, 1962-1971, undated (Box 1)
  - 1199: Drug and Hospital Union, 1970-1974, undated (Box 1)
  - 1199: Drug, Hospital and Health Care Employees Union, 1985-1989 (Box 1)
  - 1199: Drug, Hospital and Health Care Employees Union, 1986-1991 (Box 1)
  - 1199: Ephemera, 1970, 1986, undated (Box 1)
  - 1199: Hospital and Health Care Employees Union, 1988 (Box 1)
  - 1199: Hospital Division, 1958, undated (Box 1)
  - 1199: League for Practical Nurses, undated (Box 1)
  - 1199: National Health and Human Services Employees Union, 1995 (Box 1)
  - 1199: National Hospital Union, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - 1199: National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, 1973-1984, undated (Box 1, Box 49, Folder 13)
  - 1199: National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees: Membership Report, 1987 (Box 1)
  - 1199: National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees - Registered Nurses Division, 1974-1978, undated (Box 1)
  - 1199: Negotiating Committee - Columbia University, 1975 (Box 1)
  - 1199: Newspaper Clippings, 1984-1988 (Box 1)
  - 1199: Newspaper Clippings I, 1989 (Box 1)
  - 1199: Newspaper Clippings II, 1989 (Box 1)
  - 1199: Newspaper Clippings, 1990-1994, undated (Box 1)
  - 1199: Occupational Safety and Health Committee, undated (Box 1)
  - 1199: Pamphlets and Publications, 1970-1971, undated (Box 1)
  - 1199: Rank and File Activity, circa 1970s, undated (Box 1)
  - 1199: Retail Drug Employees Union, 1938-1960 (Box 1)
  - 1199: Retail Drug Employees Union - 1199 Drug News 25th Anniversary Issue, Jun 1957 (Box 1)
  - 1199: Retail Drug Employees Union - Committee to Defend the Bill of Rights, undated (Box 1)
  - 1199: Rivera, Dennis, 1990-1992 (Box 1)
  - 1199: Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 1996-2001 (Box 1)
  - 1199: United Members Committee, undated (Box 1)
  - 1199: Weekly Memorandum, 1991 (Box 1)
  - 1199-B Local (Charleston, SC), 1970, undated (Box 1)
- A, 1881-2002; 6.5 Linear Feet in 6 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Actors Equity Association, 1960-1988, undated (Box 1)
  - Ad Hoc Labor Dump Nixon Committee (New York, NY), 1972 (Box 1)
  - African Trade Union Confederation, 1965, undated (Box 1)
  - Agricultural Workers' Union: District 5, 1952 (Box 1)
  - Agricultural Workers' Union: Local 19996, undated (Box 1)
  - Air Line Employees Association, International, 1976-1978 (Box 1)
  - Air Line Employees Association, International, undated (Box 1)
  - Air Line Mechanics Association, 1939 (Box 1)
  - Air Line Pilots Association, International: Agreements, 1983-1984, undated (Box 1)
  - Air Line Pilots Association: Constitution/By-Laws, 1942-1976 (Box 2)
  - Air Line Pilots Association: Constitution/By-Laws, 1978-1984 (Box 2)
  - Air Line Pilots Association: Circular Letters, 1955-1989 (Box 2)
  - Air Line Pilots Association: Pamphlets and Publications, 1980-1990, undated (Box 2)
  - Airline Dispatchers Association, 1971-1974 (Box 2)
  - Alaskan Public Employees Association, 1980 (Box 2)
  - Albany Workingmens Assembly: Constitution and By-laws, undated (Box 2)
  - All-China Federation of Labor/Trade Unions, 1950-1960 (Box 2)
  - All-China Federation of Trade Unions, 1955, 1961 (Box 2)
  - All-India Trade Union Congress, 1953-1954, undated (Box 2)
  - All-Russian Central Council of Trade Unions, 1920 (Box 2)
  - All Unions' Committee to Shorten the Work Week, 1978 (Box 2)
  - Allgemeine Arbeiter-Union (Germany), 1927 (Box 2)
  - Alliance for Labor Action, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Alliance for Labor Action, 1969-1971, undated (Box 2)
  - Alliance of Independent Telephone Unions, undated (Box 2)
  - Allied Industrial Workers, 1964-1983 (Box 2)
  - Allied Industrial Workers, undated (Box 2)
  - Allied Industrial Workers of America: Local 209 (Milwaukee, WI), 1959 (Box 2)
  - Allied Industrial Workers of America: Local 837 (Decatur, IL), 1993, undated (Box 2)
  - Allied Printing Trades Council of Greater New York, 1917, 1941-1990, undated (Box 2)
  - Allied Printing Trades Council of New York State, 1951-1985, undated (Box 2)
  - Aluminum Workers International, 1977 (Box 2)
  - Aluminum Workers of America, 1939-1941 (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated and General Union Societies of Carpenters and Joiners (Great Britain), 1903 (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated Association of Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers of America (contains Homestead Strike article), 1921, 1936, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1933-1953 (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America: Division 241, 1937 (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America: Division 1004, 1941 (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America: Division 1277 (Los Angeles, CA), 1950 (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated Association of Street and Electric Railway Employees of America, 1928-1929 (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated Engineering Union: Australian Section, undated (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated Lithographers of America, 1950-1962, 1984, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated Lithographers of America: Constitutions, 1936-1951 (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated Lithographers of America: Constitutions, 1954-1962 (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated Lithographers of America: Local 1 (New York, NY), 1948-1970 (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated Lithographers of America: Local 1 (New York, NY), 1974-1996, undated (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, 1948-1965 (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, 1970-1975 (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, 1976-1979 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, undated (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Agreements, 1954-1972 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Constitutions, 1940-1960 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Constitutions, 1964-1976 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Department of Education, 1952-1978, undated (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Furriers Joint Council of New York, 1957-1979, undated (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Furriers Joint Council of New York: Agreements, 1958-1978 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Joint Board of Fur, Leather and Machine Workers Union, 1962, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Local 1 (Utica, NY), 1966-1974, undated (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Local 5 (San Jose, CA), 1983 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Local 56 (Meat and Cannery Workers Union) (NJ), 1946-1951 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Local 74 (New York, NY), 1969-1971 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Local 220 (Elmhurst, NY), 1979 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Local 342 (Jamaica, NY), undated (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Local 427 (Cleveland, OH), 1971 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Local 627 (New York, NY), 1960, undated (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Local 662 (Salesmen & Poultry Workers Union), c.1960s (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America: Playing Cards-Notable Union Personalities, undated (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Painters and Decorators of New York, 1897, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Sheet Metal Workers' International Alliance, 1910-1911 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Sheet Metal Workers: Local 19, 1905 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Society of House Decorators and Painters (Great Britain), 1904 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Textile Workers of America, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Trade and Labor Union of New York, 1881 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union, 1972-1990, undated (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union: Constitution/By-Laws, 1965-1979 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union: Constitution/By-Laws, 1981-1998 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union: Local 1202 (New York, NY), undated (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Union of Building Trade Workers (Great Britain), 1948 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Union of Engineering Workers (Great Britain), 1979 (Box 3)
  - Amalgamated Utility Workers, undated (Box 3)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1970-1979 (Box 3)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1980-1985 (Box 3)
  - American Communications Association I, 1940-1991, undated (Box 3)
  - American Communications Association II, 1940-1991, undated (Box 3)
  - American Communications Association: Agreements I, 1942-1964, 1984 (Box 3)
  - American Communications Association: Agreements II, 1942-1964, 1984 (Box 3)
  - American Communications Association: Constitution/By-Laws, 1938-1944 (Box 3)
  - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE): Agreements and Contracts, 1963, 1969-1970, undated (Box 3)
  - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE): Agreements and Contracts I, 1971-1978 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE): Agreements and Contracts II, 1971-1978 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE): Benefit Plans, 1978 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE): Brochures, undated (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE): Constitutions, 1941, 1960, 1970-1978 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE): Education Department, 1978 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE): Fliers, 1972-1990, undated (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE): Model Contract, undated (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE): Newspaper Clippings and Articles on, 1985 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE): Pamphlets and Publications, 1967, 1985-1991, undated (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE): Press Releases, 1991 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE): Women's Department, 1987, undated (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Grain Millers, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Grain Millers, 1990-1991 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Hosiery Workers, 1929-1938, undated (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Hosiery Workers: Constitutions, 1938-1961 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Musicians, 1949-1981 (Box 4, Box 49, Folder 2)
  - American Federation of Musicians, 1956-1990 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Musicians I, undated (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Musicians II, undated (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Musicians: Constitution/By-Laws, 1933-1950 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Musicians: Constitution/By-Laws, 1962-1977 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Musicians: Constitution/By-Laws, 1979-1989 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Musicians: Local 47, 1956 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Musicians: Local 802 (New York, NY), 1936-1967, undated (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Musicians: Local 802 (New York, NY), 1975-1992, undated (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Musicians: Local 802 (New York, NY): Constitution/By-Laws, 1962, 1965, 1967, 1977 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Musicians: Wage Scales and Conditions in the Symphony Orchestra, 1970-1981 (Box 4)
  - American Federation of Priests, 1966 (Box 5)
  - American Federation of Radio Artists, 1942 (Box 5)
  - American Federation of School Administrators, 1976-2002, undated (Box 5)
  - American Federation of School Administrators: Local 1 (Council of Supervisors and Administrators, New York, NY), 1977-1990, undated (Box 5)
  - American Federation of School Administrators: Local 1 (Council of Supervisors and Administrators, New York, NY): Agreements, 1972-1996 (Box 5)
  - American Federation of School Administrators: Local 1 (Council of Supervisors and Administrators, New York, NY): Constitution/By-Laws, 1976-2002 (Box 5)
  - American Federation of School Administrators: New York State Federation of School Administrators, 1991, c.1992 (Box 5)
  - American Federation of Technical Engineers, 1952-1960 (Box 5)
  - American Federation of Technical Engineers: Local 66 (Architectural and Engineering Guild), 1952-1972 (Box 5)
  - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), 1957-1979 (Box 5)
  - American Flint Glass Workers' Union, 1977, undated (Box 5)
  - American Flint Glass Workers' Union: Constitutions, 1942-1993 (Box 5)
  - American Guild of Variety Artists, 1944 (Box 5)
  - American Guild of Variety Artists: Constitutions, 1939-1969, undated (Box 5)
  - American Guild of Musical Artists, 1956-1978 (Box 5)
  - American Guild of Musical Artists: Constitution/By-Laws, 1947-1971, undated (Box 5)
  - American Merchant Marine Staff Officers Association, Inc., 1945 (Box 5)
  - American Nurses Association, 1975-1980, undated (Box 5)
  - American Radio Association, 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - American Radio Association: Agreements, 1948-1951 (Box 5)
  - American Radio Association: Agreements, 1953-1958 (Box 5)
  - American Radio Association: Agreements, 1961-1969 (Box 5)
  - American Radio Association: Agreements: National Agreements, 1972-1978 (Box 5)
  - American Radio Association: Constitutions, 1949-1979 (Box 5)
  - American Radio Association: Federal Communications Commission Hearing, 1954 (Box 5)
  - American Radio Association: National Assignment Rules, 1952-1970 (Box 5)
  - American Railway and Airline Supervisors Association, 1962 (Box 5)
  - American Trade Union Council for Histadrut, 1972, undated (Box 5)
  - American Train Dispatchers Association, 1917-1988, undated (Box 5)
  - Appalachian Trade Union Conference, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Asociacion Continental Americana de los Trabajadores, 1929 (Box 6)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America, 1939-1981, undated (Box 6)
  - Associated Actors and Artists of America: Constitutions, 1921-1992, undated (Box 6)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America: Italian Actors Union, 1975 (Box 6)
  - Associated Office and Professional Emergency Employees, 1934-1935, undated (Box 6)
  - Associated Fur Manufacturers, Inc., 1965 (Box 6)
  - Associated Union of the Printing Trades, undated (Box 6)
  - Association of Catholic Trade Unionists, 1941-1970 (Box 6)
  - Association of Catholic Trade Unionists: New York Chapter, 1949-1959 (Box 6)
  - Association of Civilian Technicians, 1980, 1982 (Box 6)
  - Association of Flight Attendants, 1986-1990, undated (Box 6)
  - Association of Maintenance of Way and Miscellaneous Employees, Inc., 1939-1952 (Box 6)
  - Association of Master Plumbers, 1896 (Box 6)
  - Association of Professional Engineering Personnel, 1956 (Box 6)
  - Association of Professional Executive, Clerical and Computer Staff (APEX) (Great Britain), 1974 (Box 6)
  - Association of Railway Executives, undated (Box 6)
  - Association of Supervisory Staffs and Engineering Technicians (ASSET) (Great Britain), undated (Box 6)
  - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers, 1966-1983, undated (Box 6)
  - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers: Constitutions, 1974-1995 (Box 6)
  - Association Western Union Employees, 1930, 1933 (Box 6)
  - Atlanta Allied Printing Trades Council (GA), 1979 (Box 6)
  - Atlantic Maritime Employees Union, 1940, undated (Box 6)
  - Atlantic Maritime Officers Association, 1941 (Box 6)
  - Australian Council of Trade Unions, undated (Box 6)
  - Australian Manufacturing Workers' Union, undated (Box 6)
  - Australian Union of Students, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Authors' League of America, undated (Box 6)
- B, 1883-1997; 4.5 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Barbers and Beauty Culturists Union of America, 1939, 1949, 1952 (Box 6)
  - Barbers, Beauticians, and Allied Industries International Association, undated (Box 6)
  - Bell Aircraft Workers: Committee to Aid in the Legal Defense of the Bell Workers (Buffalo, NY), circa 1949 (Box 6)
  - Bookkeepers, Stenographers and Accountants' Union, undated (Box 6)
  - Boot and Shoeworkers' Union, 1898, 1933, 1961 (Box 6)
  - Boston Central Labor Union, 1935 (Box 6)
  - Bottlers and Drivers Union: No. 347, 1918 (Box 6)
  - Brewery Workers Joint Local Executive Board of Greater New York, undated (Box 6)
  - Brewery Workers United, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Bricklayer and Allied Craftworkers: Local 1 (New York, NY), undated (Box 6)
  - Bricklayers and Masons' International Union of America, 1895 (Box 6)
  - Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers International Union of America, 1940-1970, undated (Box 6)
  - Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers International Union of America: Constitutions, 1942-1959 (Box 6)
  - Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers International Union of America: Constitutions, 1960-1970, undated (Box 6)
  - Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers International Union of America: Local 88 (Tile Layers Helpers Union) (NY), 1982 (Box 6)
  - British Guiana Trades Union Council, 1964 (Box 6)
  - British Iron, Steel and Kindred Trades Association, 1917 (Box 6)
  - British Mineworkers Union, undated (Box 6)
  - Bronx Union Label Club, undated (Box 6)
  - Brooklyn Central Labor Union, 1915 (Box 6)
  - Brooklyn Metal Trades Council, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Brotherhood of Consolidated Edison Employees: Locals 1-4: Contracts, 1940-1946 (Box 6)
  - Brotherhood of Consolidated Edison Employees: Local 1-5, 1940-1944 (Box 6)
  - Brotherhood of Edison Employees, 1932 (Box 6)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.), 1918-1923, 1947-1966 (Box 6)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.), 1974-1977 (Box 6)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.), 1977-1990, undated (Box 6)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1898-1919 (Box 6)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1927-1965, undated (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen: Constitutions, 1909-1948, undated (Box 7)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance Way Employes, 1937-1959 (Box 7)